

# **NOAH BORG**

noahborg122801@yahoo.com | (313) 398-9948 | Taylor, MI 48180

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Passionate and driven programmer with the eagerness to learn and gain experience with a company. While competent, I am driven to learn to further my skills and understanding of all things coding. Quick to learn, as well as able to focus on multiple tasks at once while prioritizing the most important. I am excited to better any company that I have the pleasure of being at, and hope the employees around me can help better myself.

### SKILLS

- Full Stack-Coding with a focus in JavaScript and React
- Experience in both MySQL and MongoDB
- Experience with CSS and Bootstrap elements

### **WORK HISTORY**

**Security Officer** | The Henry Ford Museum Of 10/2022 - CURRENT American Innovation - Dearborn, MI

Midnight Security of The Henry Ford Museum and Green Field Village, Monitoring Rooms, Cameras, and Maintaining Security

Intern | Third Judicial District - Detroit, MI 08/2021 - 12/2021

Observe Court Room, Ask Questions

**Crew Member** | Taco Bell - Dundee, MI 08/2018 - 06/2019

Customer Service and Cleaning

#### **EDUCATION**

Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI

03/2023

Certificate in Full-Stack Coding: Computer Science